xsexwale.com 2017-05-07

# PRIVACY POLICY

At xsexwale.com the privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that are received and collected and how it is used.

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

## **1\. Log Files**

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:  
* Internet Protocol addresses (IP)  
* Types of browser  
* Internet Service Provider (ISP)  
* Date and time stamp  
* Referring and exit pages  
* Number of clicks  
All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

## 2\. Cookies

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, xsexwale.com has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

## 3\. Other

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address for receiving communication from us. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy  please feel free to contact us by email at   **soniyaduston786@gmail.com**
